printsasia.com 2014-11-22

# Privacy Policy : Printsasia USA : Printsasia.com

Printsasia is committed to safeguard its users' privacy. We request all our users to read the following 'privacy policy' to understand how their personal & business information will be treated, as they make full use of our services to their benefit. This policy is applicable to all the visitors and customers of Printsasia.com 

#### Your Privacy is our Concern

We are committed to protect your privacy in all aspects of our business. Every information we collect from you is completely secure and we do not sell or disclose this to any third party unless compelled by the law of the land. Any change in privacy policy is immediately updated on our website. We maintain 100% transparency in the usage of data we collect through surfers' activities on our website. Please check back periodically, to update yourself with change in our privacy policy, if any. 

#### What Information We Collect and How We Use It?

Printsasia collects information from its users when they register to gain access to our services or at other specific instances when they are requested to provide us with their personal & business information. During registration, we ask the users for their name, email address, business information and other personal details. Once a user registers, he/she is no longer anonymous to Printsasia and it is deemed that the user has given Printsasia the right to use the details for receiving, including but not limited to, catalogs, periodicals, Newsletters and other promotional materials as designed by Printsasia team. 

When you are on our network and are asked for personal information, you are sharing the information with Printsasia alone, unless it is specifically stated otherwise. If in any instance the data will be shared with any third party, you will be notified prior to the time of data collection or transfer. You can decide not to participate in the promotion if you don't want your data to be shared. 

#### Sharing of Information

As a general rule, Printsasia will not disclose or share any of the user's personally identifiable information except when Printsasia has the user's permission or under special circumstances, such as when Printsasia believes in good faith that the law requires it or as permitted in terms of this policy. 

Printsasia may also disclose account information in special cases when Printsasia has reasons to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating Printsasia Terms of Services or may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) Printsasia's rights or property, other Printsasia network website users, or if Printsasia deems it necessary to maintain, service, and improve its products and services. 

#### Distribution of Information

Printsasia may, from time to time, send its users emails regarding its products and services. In addition, Printsasia may occasionally send direct mails about products and services that it feels may be of interest to the user. Only Printsasia or its agents working under confidentiality agreements will send these direct mailings. 

#### Links to other Websites

The Printsasia Web site may contain links to other sites, operated by third parties, that we think may be of interest to you. Printsasia encourages third parties to follow appropriate privacy standards and policies, but is not responsible for the actions of those parties, the content of their Web sites, or any products or services they may offer. 

#### Editing or Updating Information

A user may edit his/her account information and profile by logging onto our website and/or by sending a request to [web@printsasia.com](mailto:web@printsasia.com). The requested changes may take upto 24Hrs to appear online because of verification process and server cache policies. 

A user account can be deleted or deactivated, but doing so will result in the user not being able to access any members-only area of the network. Residual information will remain within our archive records. 

#### Protection of information

As with all information, Printsasia will never sell any user's personal or business information until and unless it is permitted by the user. Any user statistics that we may provide to prospective advertisers or partners regarding product or service usage on Printsasia network is provided in an aggregate form only and does not include any personally identifiable information about any individual user. 

We request our users to sign out of their Printsasia account and close their browser window when they have finished their work. This is to ensure that others cannot access their personal or business information and correspondence, if the user shares the computer with someone else or is using a computer in a public place. Printsasia takes necessary steps, within its limits of commercial viability and necessity, to ensure that the user's information is treated securely. 

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while Printsasia strives to protect the user's personal & business information, it cannot ensure the security of any information transmitted to Printsasia and you do so at your own risk. Once Printsasia receives your transmission, it makes best efforts to ensure its security in its systems. 

#### Protection of information While Ordering and Shipping

To order from us, you must set up an account. Setting up an account requires you to provide your e-mail address and to choose a password (your "Account Information"). When you order from us, we also ask for your name, shipping address, telephone number, and your credit card number, billing address, and expiration date (your "Order Information"). This information is necessary for us to process your order, to notify you of your order status, and to fulfill orders. 

To process and fulfill orders, we provide your mailing details to shipping/postal or courier companies, but do not provide any more personal information such as your e-mail address or billing information. The above mentioned third parties may not use your personal information for any purpose other than those related to the fulfillment of your order. 

#### Cookies & Display Advertising

We have updated our site with the Google Analytics features for Display Advertising, which will let Analytics to collect data about our site's traffic via the DoubleClick cookie in addition to data collected through the standard Google Analytics implementation. 

For visitors, here are some important points to understand about Display Advertising: 

  * The features for Display Advertising will be automatically implemented for every visitors, as it works through cookie, which is a small piece of information stored by a web server on a web browser so it can be read back later from that browser. 
  * These features are based on Displayed Advertising (e.g., Remarketing). 
  * If you don't want to be tracked, you can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads for you by using the [Ads Preferences Manager.](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/?hl=en&sig=ACi0TCj1XU3L94ucOhQwaPlXDBoOkjDMqKICKxe6CysCQOpRRBWxlWf4B13kAQdZQ1HYSInyXFXLdvu1-XsdAkRoGC5Ul5bhplea9Oe0-vEdS9UegmU-a-ebqibeWzEZ-zlah_k1cdx68GfdhXHdD9zKs4ThxY8NOgMs8YEsRZted7N9HkD8ylY)

#### Changes in Privacy Policy

The policy may change from time to time so please check periodically
